Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 1: Historic Image Collection
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Houses (2720 Dumbarton Street, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 723)
      Garden of the Joseph W. Alsop House in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (2720 Dumbarton Street, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 724)
      Exterior of Joseph W. Alsop House in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (3053 P Street, NW, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 725)
      Sculpture in garden at the Cabot Coville House in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 726)
    - Houses (2815 Dumbarton Street, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 727)
      Garden of Mrs. Julian Larcombe Schley House in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (2815 Dumbarton Street, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 728)
      Exterior of Mrs. Julian Larcombe Schley House in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Markets (Wisconsin Avenue and Van Ness Street, Georgetown), 1971 April (Item 729)
      Outdoor flower market (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1964 June (Item 730)
      Cascading fountain in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1964 June (Item 731)
      Statue of Dante by Ettore Ximenes in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1964 June (Item 732)
      People walking near cascading fountain in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1970 May (Item 733)
      Trees surrounding statue of Dante by Ettore Ximenes in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1969 April (Item 734)
      Joan of Arc statue by Paul Dubois in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1969 April (Item 735)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1969 April (Item 736)
      Globe sculpture and cascading fountain in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1969 April (Item 737)
      View from atop the cascading fountain in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), 1951 June 17 (Item 738)
      President James Buchanan Memorial by Hans Schuler in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 739)
      Globe sculpture and cascading fountain in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: J. Criscione)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 740)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 741)
      People on staircase in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 742)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 743)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 744)
    - Houses (16th Street and Florida Avenue, NW), Ca. 1949 (Item 745)
      View of Henderson Castle (Torn down in 1949) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 746)
      Flowers in Meridian Hill Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (16th and W Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 747)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1960 June (Item 748)
      Flowers at the US National Arboretum (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1963 October (Item 749)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1960 June (Item 750)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 June (Item 751)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1960 June (Item 752)
      Woman taking picture of the flowers at the US National Arboretum (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1960 June (Item 753)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1963 October (Item 754)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 May (Item 755)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 May (Item 756)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 May (Item 757)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 May (Item 758)
    - Parks (3501 New York Avenue, NE), 1967 May (Item 759)
      Blooming trees at the US National Arboretum (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 760)
      Firefighters working to put out fire in the chicken house at the Soldiers' Home (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 761)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 762)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 763)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 764)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 765)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 766)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 767)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 768)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 769)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 770)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 771)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 772)
    - Fire (Soldiers' Home, 3700 North Capitol Street, NW), 1957 April 14 (Item 773)
    - Mayflower II, 1958 May (Item 774)
      View of an exhibit on the Pilgrims (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Mayflower II, 1958 May (Item 775)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Mayflower II, 1958 May (Item 776)
    - Mayflower II (Potomac River), 1958 May (Item 777)
      People touring replica of the Mayflower docked in Washington area (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Mayflower II (Potomac River), 1958 May (Item 778)
    - Mayflower II (Potomac River), 1958 May (Item 779)
    - Mayflower II (Potomac River), 1958 May (Item 780)
    - Santa Maria (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 781)
      People touring replica of the Santa Maria docked in Washington area (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Santa Maria (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 782)
    - Santa Maria (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 783)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1960 May (Item 784)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal near unknown lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal - 11710 MacArthur Blvd., Potomac, MD), 1960 May (Item 785)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal and Great Fall Tavern lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1960 May (Item 786)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1960 May (Item 787)
      Bridge over Chesapeake and Ohio Canal with canoe in canal (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), Ca. 1950 (Item 788)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal near unknown lock, showing lock house (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), Ca. 1950 (Item 789)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal in Georgetown, car barn in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1948 April 15 (Item 790)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1961 April (Item 791)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal in Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal - 11710 MacArthur Blvd., Potomac, MD), 1974 January (Item 792)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1974 January (Item 793)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal at unknown lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal - 11710 MacArthur Blvd., Potomac, MD), 1974 January (Item 794)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1965 October (Item 795)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1964 April (Item 796)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1965 October (Item 797)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1965 October (Item 798)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1965 October (Item 799)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1964 April (Item 800)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal at Georgetown lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1963 October (Item 801)
      Mule pulling boat, with people walking along Chesapeake and Ohio Canal path (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1963 October (Item 802)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Near Georgetown (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1963 October (Item 803)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1963 October (Item 804)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1963 October (Item 805)
      View of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1963 October (Item 806)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal), 1963 October (Item 807)
    - C and O Canal (C and O Canal, Georgetown), 1965 October (Item 808)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 809)
      View of the falls with people out on the rocks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 810)
      View of the Virginia side of the falls (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 811)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 812)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 813)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 814)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 815)
      People walking on a path near the falls, Virginia side (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 816)
    - Great Falls (Potomac River), 1967 July (Item 817)
    - Festivals (14th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1972 August (Item 818)
      Street scene at the DC Folk Festival, man with balloons (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 819)
      Boy looking at display of geese decoys (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 820)
      People looking at two docked skipjacks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 821)
      Chesapeake oyster dredge on deck of ship (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 822)
      Bow of the skipjack "H. M. Krentz" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 823)
      People looking at docked skipjacks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 824)
      Bow of the skipjack (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 825)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 826)
    - Festivals, 1972 August (Item 827)
      Festival of American Folklife sign (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (National Mall), 1972 August (Item 828)
      Fruit stand on the National Mall during folk festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (National Mall), 1972 July (Item 829)
    - Festivals, 1972 August (Item 830)
      Horse being walked during festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 831)
      Musicians on stage during folk festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 832)
    - Festivals (Hains Point/East Potomac Park), 1972 August (Item 833)
      Two men sitting behind table filled with bird decoys (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals, 1968 July (Item 834)
      Blacksmith working during folk festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Festivals (Smithsonian Institution Museum of Natural History), 1968 July (Item 835)
      Children playing on dinosaur outside Museum of Natural History on National Mall (Photographer: Unknown)
- Series 2: Martin Mooney
  These images include nineteen slides of the Cherry Blossom parade, twenty of the Moscow Circus bear wedding on the National Mall, four of the altar for the Pope's mass on the Mall, and four of an artist with his large sculpture of a boot.
  - Mooney (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1001)
      Pom pom girls of unidentified school band during Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1002)
      South Carolina float at Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1003)
      Georgia float at Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1004)
      Shriner Chanters float at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1005)
      Unidentified high school marching band at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1006)
      Texas float at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1007)
      Arkansas float at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1008)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1009)
      Walter Washington in police motorcycle sidecar at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1010)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1011)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1012)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1013)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1014)
      Large balloon animal at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1015)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1016)
      Cherry Blossom Festival Princess on float at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1017)
      Clowns at the Cherry Blossom Parade (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1018)
    - Parade (Constitution Avenue), 1970 (Item 1019)
    - Pope's Altar (National Mall), 1979 October 5 (Item 1020)
      Sunrise over altar for Pope's mass on the mall - US Capitol in background (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Pope's Altar (National Mall), 1979 October 5 (Item 1021)
    - Pope's Altar (National Mall), 1979 October 5 (Item 1022)
    - Pope's Altar (National Mall), 1979 October 5 (Item 1023)
    - Big Boots (12th Street, NW), 1979 September (Item 1024)
      Big Boots with artists (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
  - Mooney (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Big Boots (12th Street, NW), 1979 September (Item 1025)
    - Big Boots (12th Street, NW), 1979 September (Item 1026)
    - Big Boots (12th Street, NW), 1979 September (Item 1027)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1028)
      Trainer with groom bear at Moscow Circus Russian bears' wedding (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1029)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1030)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1031)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1032)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1033)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1034)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1035)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1036)
      Trainers with bride and groom bears at Moscow Circus Russian bears' wedding (Photographer: Martin Mooney)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1037)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1038)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1039)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1040)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1041)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1042)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1043)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1044)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1045)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1046)
    - Moscow Bears (National Mall), 1978 January (Item 1047)
- Series 3: Lori Federman
  This series includes thirteen images of the US Treasury building and four of the White House.
  - Federman (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2001)
      North entrance of US Treasury Department building and Albert Gallatin (Photographer: Unknown)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2002)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2003)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2004)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2005)
      North entrance of US Treasury Department building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2006)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2007)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2008)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2009)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2010)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2011)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2012)
    - US Treasury (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2013)
    - White House (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2014)
      South side of the White House (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2015)
    - White House (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2016)
    - White House (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1979 December (Item 2017)
- Series 4: Roy Watson
  Four images of the development at Fort Lincoln.
  - Watson (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fort Lincoln (Knox hill, 7th District), 1987 September (Item 3001)
      Unidentified policeman, man and two women at construction site (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fort Lincoln (Knox hill, 7th District), 1987 September (Item 3002)
      Apartment building under construction (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fort Lincoln (Knox hill, 7th District), 1987 September (Item 3003)
      Unidentified policeman and two women at construction site (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fort Lincoln (Knox hill, 7th District), 1987 September (Item 3004)
- Series 5: Chamber of Commerce
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4000)
      View of crowd at Reflecting Pool from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4001)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4002)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4003)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4004)
      Male speaker (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4005)
      Family walking in front of Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4006)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4007)
      Pete Seeger and man in front of Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4008)
      Gloria Steinem (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4009)
      Pete Seeger and man with microphone in front of Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4010)
      Men looking at brochures below "Socialist Labor Party" banner (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4011)
      People marching with signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4012)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4013)
      People looking at books below "Jobs, Not War!" banner (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4014)
      Coretta Scott King (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4015)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Hoover Building, 1401 Constitution Ave, NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4016)
      People marching with banner, "Dennis Serrette for President; Consumer Party 1984" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Hoover Building, 1401 Constitution Ave, NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4017)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Hoover Building, 1401 Constitution Ave, NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4018)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4019)
      View of crowd at Reflecting Pool from Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4020)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4021)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4022)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4023)
      View of crowd at Reflecting Pool (Photographer: David Valdez)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4024)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4025)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4026)
      View of cameramen on bleachers (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4027)
      Tony Bonilla (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4028)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4029)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4030)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4031)
      Martin Luther King, Sr. and grandchildren (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4032)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4033)
      Male speaker (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4034)
      Maynard Jackson (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4035)
      Maynard Jackson (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4036)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4037)